[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Kyle：所以就像那个快速回顾一样，这真的是关于加号的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle: So just as that quick review, this is really all about plus.
这是AND，不是OR。
This is an and, not an or.
我们需要回拨和重击。
We want callbacks and thunks.
我们需要承诺和发电机，以及可观测的，和CSP。
We want promises and generators, and observables, and CSP.
我们希望所有这些工具都能为我们所用，
We want all these tools available to us,
因为这会让我们成为更好的开发者。
cuz that's gonna make us better developers.
好吗？
Okay?
作为提醒，这是我的联系信息。
As a reminder this is my contact information.
我强烈鼓励和
I strongly encourage and
挑战你不要让这是你最后一次复习材料。
challenge you to not let this be the last time you go over the material.
几周后回到这些练习中，从头开始尝试。
Go back to these exercises in a couple of weeks and try them from scratch.
回去复习幻灯片，复习你的笔记。
Go back over the slides, over your notes.
尝试这些事情，并尝试将它们融入你正在做的工作中。
Try these things and try to work them into the work that you're doing.
即使你认为你的老板是这样的，
Even if you think you have a boss who is like,
他永远不会在乎我在做这种事，这并不意味着
he'll never care that I'm doing this kinda stuff, that doesn't mean that
你不能把你在工作中做的事情当作学习更好的机会。
you can't use the stuff that you do at work as an opportunity to learn better.
即使你试图把东西拿出来，即使代码永远不会被提交进去，
Even if you're trying and stuff out, and even if that code never gets committed in,
更好的是你在上下文中尝试并从中学习。
and it's still better that you try it in context and learn from that.
当你学到东西的时候，如果你学到了什么，我会鼓起你的勇气
And I'd courage you that when you learn something, if you've learned something
今天在这里，或者当你回去的时候，如果你觉得你学到了什么
here today, or if you feel like you learned something when you go back over
一些东西，去写两到三段关于它的博客帖子。
some stuff, go write a little two or three paragraph blog post about it.
试着教别人。
Try to teach someone else.
因为当你被迫去教别人的时候，你真的学得最好。
Because you really learn best, when you're forced to try to teach somebody else.
所以无论你的领域是什么
So whatever your realm is,
你不一定要在你的职称中有“教师”这个词才能成为一名教师。
you don't have to have the word teacher in your job title to be a teacher.
你可以写一篇博客文章，你可以去开会讨论它，然后
You can write a blog post, you can go to a meet up and talk about it, and
做一个闪电般的演讲，写一本关于它的书。
give a lightning talk about it, write a book about it.
我的意思是，做你想做的事，但是在工作中给一个棕色的袋子午餐，说嘿，我只是
I mean, do whatever you wanna do, but give a brown bag lunch at work, say hey I just
去了这个工作坊，让我给你看看我学到的一些东西，对吧？
went to this workshop, let me show you some of the stuff that I learned, right?
这就是你如何巩固学习，
That is how you'll solidify the learning,
就是练习这些东西然后教别人。
is to practice those things then teach others.
所以在经历这些事情的过程中，如果你有任何问题
So in that process of going through those things, if you ever have any questions you
今天感到不知所措，你知道你想绕回来，
feel overwhelmed by something today, and you know you wanna circle back,
当你想回去的时候，你对此有一些疑问。
and you've got some questions about it, when you want to go back.
请随时联系，
Please feel free to reach out,
有几十种不同的方法可以联系到我。
there's dozens of different ways to get a hold of me.
我喜欢做这个。
I love doing this.
这就是我，我全身心投入教学的事情，
This is what I, I'm all in on the teaching thing,
试图帮助人们更好地理解JavaScript。
trying to help people understand JavaScript better.
能来到这里真是莫大的荣幸。
It's been a super huge honor to be here.
我很感谢你们的关注和
I appreciate all of your attention and
坚持下去，通过一堆具有挑战性的材料。
sticking with it, through a bunch of challenging material.
非常感谢您来到这里，并祝您学习JavaScript愉快。
Thanks very much for being here, and happy JavaScript learning.